heidicohen.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Heidi Cohen

### Your Information

The Actionable Marketing Guide respects your privacy. Your email address, name and any other information you provide to the Actionable Marketing Guide are held in strict confidence. We only keep your information so that we can send you email keeping you informed on subjects that may interest you.

**We will not sell or share your information with anyone else.**

We will retain your personal data for as long as needed in order to provide services to you. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Unsubscribing

If you are a subscriber to one of our email lists and would no longer like to be contacted by us, please use the link provided at the end of our newsletter to unsubscribe. If that option is not available, contact us directly by sending an email to <[postmaster@heidicohen.com](mailto:postmaster@heidicohen.com)> with the word, UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line. Please allow a few business days for processing your request.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as your name and email address, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can [contact us](https://heidicohen.com/contact/).

### Social Media

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our website. It may also set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. Your interaction with any of these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Links

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by our website.

### Comments

Our website offers a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide by commenting on a blog post may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog [contact us](https://heidicohen.com/contact/).

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via email to <[postmaster@heidicohen.com](mailto:postmaster@heidicohen.com)>.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

### Notifications

We may update our privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Acknowledgements

Our thanks to [Aweber.com](https://aweber.com/?433831), our email newsletter service provider, for allowing us to incorporate language from their privacy policy into ours.
